[{
	"rs": [
		{
			"question": "Which tavern is found in Falador?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Blue Moon Inn",
				"b": "Pick and Lute",
				"c": "Rising Sun",
				"d": "Poison Arrow"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "c",
			"explanation": "The Blue Moon Inn is found in Varrock, the Pick and Lute in Taverley, and the Poison Arrow in Ardougne."
		}, {
			"question": "According to the natural history quiz in the Varrock Museum, how did wyverns die out?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Climate change",
				"b": "Disease",
				"c": "Marauding adventurers",
				"d": "Janet Reno"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a"
		}, {
			"question": "Count Draynor, weakened after isolation from Morytania, is killed by the player during Vampyre Slayer. Which vampyre is he related to?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Alexei Jovkai",
				"b": "Vanstrom Klause",
				"c": "Tenebra Remanis",
				"d": "Vanescula Drakan"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "d",
			"explanation": "Count Draynor Drakan also has two brothers, Lowerniel Drakan and Ranis Drakan."
		}, {
			"question": "Which tree in RuneScape is a misspelling of a real-life tree?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Acadia tree",
				"b": "Sassafras tree",
				"c": "Eucalyptus tree",
				"d": "Dramen tree"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"explanation": "Acadia is an accidental misspelling of acacia; the developers decided to keep it because they liked it better."
		}, {
			"question": "During which quest does Sigmund tie Zanik to the tracks of the Dorgesh-Kaanâ€“Keldagrim train system?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Another Slice of H.A.M.",
				"b": "Death to the Dorgeshuun",
				"c": "Land of the Goblins",
				"d": "The Chosen Commander"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a"
		}, {
			"question": "Who founded the Moon Clan?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Pauline Polaris",
				"b": "The Oneiromancer",
				"c": "Janet Reno",
				"d": "V"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "c",
			"explanation": "Janet Reno was an American lawyer who served as the Attorney General of the United States from 1993 until 2001 under Bill Clinton."
		}, {
			"question": "Kranon the Ambassador, corrupted after a ritual that summoned Xau-Tak, was originally a member of which race?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Naragi",
				"b": "Dragonkin",
				"c": "Chthonians",
				"d": "Ilujanka"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"explanation": "\"Kerapac objects, of course. As do some of the remaining council. . . . They tell me that it's dark magic. That there is something wrong about it. . . . Let them rant. I go now to create a new future, free from chains, where we can forge our own destiny.\""
		}, {
			"question": "Of the four following cities, which one is furthest south?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Yanille",
				"b": "Al Kharid",
				"c": "Brimhaven",
				"d": "Lletya"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a"
		}, {
			"question": "Which spell was used to summon Zamorak during Evil Dave's Big Day Out?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Um nahi listic durooo-rah",
				"b": "Carlem Aber Camerinthum Purchai Gabindo",
				"c": "Dominoes Ad Nauseum, Romanes Eunt Domus",
				"d": "Ika tha nke rius Zanka Tdaterius"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"explanation": "The same spell was previously used in the Demon Slayer quest, before it was reworked in 2013, to banish the demon Delrith (albeit with the words in random order)."
		}, {
			"question": "The God Wars Dungeon, frozen for thousands of years, eventually thawed in the Fifth Age. Who rediscovered the temple and its combatants?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "The Temple Knights",
				"b": "The White Knights",
				"c": "Orlando Smith",
				"d": "Drunken Dwarf"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "d",
			"explanation": "A letter written by Sir Gerry, who lies dying outside the entrance to the God Wars Dungeon, describes his efforts to \"investigate the dwarf's drunken claims\"."
		}
	],
	"osrs": [
		{
			"question": "Which game is better?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "RuneScape",
				"b": "Old School RuneScape",
				"c": "RuneScape Classic",
				"d": "Fortnite"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "d",
			"explanation": "lmao"
		}, {
			"question": "How many administrators are there on the Old School RuneScape Wiki?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "8",
				"b": "12",
				"c": "16",
				"d": "20"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "c"
		}
	]
}]